JIN KUAN MOO

https://minahhh666.github.io/ https://www.linkedin.com/in/jin-kuan-moo/

Summary

A UCD Computer Science Master proficient in Chinese Mandarin, English, and Malay. Full stack development experience in several languages as well as Agile methodology. Great networking (TCP/IP), OS (Windows, Linux) and machine learning knowledge. Previously worked as a manufacturing manager, leading a team of 20 engaged in daily production. Volunteered in Code in Place hosted by Stanford University, delivering online Python lessons to a group of 15 students. An excellent team player with great team management and communications skills.

Email: jkmoo0412@hotmail.com

Mobile: 0892059402

Education

University College Dublin Dublin, Ireland MSc Computer Science; GPA:3.82 Sep 2022 – Dec 2023

University College Dublin Dublin, Ireland BSc Food Science; GPA:3.77 Sep 2017 – Jun 2021

Experience

Stanford University Dublin, Ireland Section Leader Apr 2023 – Jun 2023

• Participating in Code in Place, an online introductory coding course

- Conducting weekly lessons for a cohort of 15 students
- Teaching topics including Python, Animations, Console Programming, Graphic Programming etc.

Krispy Kreme Kildare, Ireland Sep 2021 - Jun 2022

Manufacturing Manager

- Managing a 20-member team for daily production operations
 - Ensuring adherence to safety protocols, HACCP principles, and legal regulations
 - Maintaining accurate inventory control, yield records, and traceability documents

Projects

Afterparty

an event impact analysis tool which provides insights into how the busyness of urban areas are impacted by largescale event.

- Utilized React.js, Mapbox GL.js, and Figma for the frontend development
- Implemented the backend with Node.js, Express.js, Flask, and Apache
- Developed prediction models using Random Forest and XGBoost

Dublin Bikes

a web application providing real-time information and journey planning for bike-sharing services.

- Utilized Vanilla JS, HTML, CSS, and Google Maps API for frontend development
- Implemented the backend with Flask, MySQL, AWS EC2, AWS RDS, Gunicorn, Nginx
- Developed prediction models using Linear Regression

Asteroids

a classic arcade video game which player controls a spaceship in an asteroid field to destroy incoming asteroids.

- Developed using Java
- Used JavaFX as the GUI framework

Technical Skills

- Programming languages: Python, JavaScript, Java, Ruby, HTML, CSS, TypeScript, Object-oriented
- Frameworks: React.js, Flask, Express.js, JavaFX, Pygame
- Database: MySQL, AWS RDS
- OS: Linux, Windows
- Tools: VSCode, Jupyter Notebook, GitHub, Microsoft Office, GCP, AWS, WordPress, Apache Maven, Docker
- Machine Learning: Linear Regression, Logistic Regression, Random Forest, XGBoost, KNN, Scikit-learn
- Others: Data Structures and Algorithms, Object-Oriented Programming, Networking (TCP/IP), REST API